{
    "question": "Change the affirmative sentences into negative sentences(we saw some good show in wonogiri)",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "We saw some very bad show in wonogiri<br><br><br>*Maaf kalo salah",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "We saw some bad show in wonogiri",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "tolong-ceritakan-kembali-cerita-di-bawah-ini-240",
            "question": "Tolong ceritakan kembali cerita di bawah ini !    \u00a0\r\n\r\n \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 The greedy dog\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 One day, a dog stole a big piece of meat and he was very\r\n proud of it. Then, he ran off until he reached the bank of the river. He looked\r\n down into the river water carefully and he saw another dog with a piece of meat\r\n in its mouth.\r\n\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 Funnily enough, the dog did not realize that it was his own\r\n reflection\u00a0 in the water. When he was\r\n full, he threw himself on the other dog to steal his meat as well.\r\n Unfortunately, when he was in the water, he had to let go the remains of the\r\n meat to avoid drowning, and so was left with nothing.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Anjing yang serakah<br><br>suatu hari si anjing mencuri daging yang sangat besar, dan ia bangga karna itu. Lalu ia berlari sampai ia menapai sungai yang besar. Iamelihat ke air sungai dengan hati-hati. Lalu ia melihat anjing yang di mulutnya terdapat daging yang besar.<br>Lucunya, si aning tidak menyadari bahwa itu adalah pantulan dirinya sendiri.<br>Saat ia penuh, ia melempari dirinya sendiri ke anjing lainnya untuk mencuri daging milik si anjing itu. Sayangnya saat di air, ia melepaskan sisa-sisa daging agar tidak tenggelam. Jadi yang tertinggal tidak ada apa-apa<br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-present-tense-yang-menggunakan-rumus-nominal-396",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat present tense yang menggunakan rumus nominal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "i am a student<br>it is an elephant<br><br>subject+to be+complement",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buatin-dialog-narative-cerita-rakyat-4-pemain-976",
            "question": "Tolong buatin dialog narative cerita rakyat 4 pemain\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<br><br>\n\nOne day while a mousedeer was\nwalking in the forest, he saw a big black snake sleeping under the tree. When\nhe saw the snake, the mousedeer was frightened. When he wanted to run away from\nthe snake, he suddenly fell on top of a tiger which was sleeping not far from\nthe snake. The tiger woke up and took of the mousedeer. He told the mousedeer\nthat he was going to eat him for lunch. \u201cPlease don\u2019t eat me now,\u201d said the\nmousedeer. \u201cI have something important to do.\u201d\n\n<span>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 \u201cLook,\u201d\nsaid the mousedeer. \u201cThat is the king\u2019s belt. He asked me to stay here and\nwatch it while he was away in the forest.\u201d The tiger looked at the snake and\nsaid, \u201cThat is a beautiful belt. I need a belt like that. Can I wear it?\u201d He\nasked the mousedeer.</span>\n\n<span>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 \u201cOh\nall right,\u201d said the mousedeer. So he picked up the snake and winded it around\nthe tiger. Then the snake woke up and saw the tiger. The snake twisted itself\ntighter until the tiger couldn\u2019t breathe. The tiger asked the mousedeer to help\nhim. But the mousedeer turned and ran away into the forest.</span>\n\n\u00a0\n\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "mother : its been a while I havent seen my son, but now i could see him standing here in front of me with all the achievement<br>malin kundang : but you are not my mom, i come from rich family<br>wife: malin but he looks like you<br>ship crew : yes bos, u should not deny it",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-binggris-nya-pertama-tama-marilah-kita-panjatkan-syukur-kepa-155",
            "question": "Apa b.inggris nya pertama-tama marilah kita panjatkan syukur kepada tuhan",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "first,we must thanks giving to<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "First thanks giving let us to god",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-bahasa-inggris-mengenai-belajar-677",
            "question": "Contoh dialog bahasa inggris mengenai belajar",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "a: hi,... (name your friend)<br>b: owh hi too (your name)<br>a: why did you come late to school today?<br>b: huuff... about it, overnight my homework until late at night and it makes me wake up late.<br>a: owh,.. hahaha... so that&#039;s the reason why you come too late?<br>b: yess..<br><br>#maaf kalau jelek xp<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "manakah-yang-lebih-sulit-bahasa-indonesia-atau-bahasa-inggris-443",
            "question": "Manakah yang lebih sulit, bahasa indonesia atau bahasa inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "bahasa inggris pastinya",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "kalau menurut saya bahasa inggris karena kita kan orang indonesia jadi lebih sulit mempelajari bahasa dari negara lain.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "once-happy-monkey-dance-at-gatherings-of-animals-and-they-are-936",
            "question": "\u00a0 Once happy monkey dance at gatherings of animals, and they are    all very pleased with his performance that they elected him their king. A\r\n Fox, envying him the honor, discovered a piece of meat lying in a trap,\r\n and leading the Monkey to the spot, said that he had found a shop in \r\n the woods, but do not use it, he had been saving for him as treasure \r\n trove of his kingdom, and counseled him to seize it .\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n \u00a0 Monkey approached carelessly and was caught in a trap, and on his \r\n accusing the Fox deliberately took him into a trap, he replied, \"Oh \r\n Monkey, and you, with your mind like you, will be the King of animals\r\n\r\napa arti dari cerita di atas?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "sebuah **** sedang berdansa di tengah perkumpulan hewan, semua sangat \nsenang karena ***** tersebut terpilih menjadi raja, sang rubah yang \ntidak mengakui kekuasaan keledai mempersiapkan sebuah jebakan dengan \nmenaruh sebuah daging dan membawa *** tersebut pergi ke tempat itu \ndengan berkata bahwa dia menemukan hadiah di dalam pohon, tapi dia tidak\n mau memakainya dia menyimpannya karena untuk harta karun di kerajaannya\n dan menyarankan ***** itu untuk memakainya. ***** itu datang dengan \nceroboh dan tertangkap oleh jebakannya rubah, dan rubah berkata dengan \npikiranmu yang seperti itu, akankah kamu menjadi raja?<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-recount-text-dalam-bahasa-inggris-dialog-6-org-772",
            "question": "Contoh dialog recount text dalam bahasa inggris (dialog 6 org)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "\u00a0Fadli: Hi Dina, long time no see you. You do not come together with Handi?<br>Dina: Yes, I&#039;m with Handi, he was buying something out there.<br>Handi: Fadli, how are you?<br>Fadli: Finally you come, I&#039;ve been waiting for a long time. I&#039;m fine, how about you?<br>Handi: I&#039;m very well today and am very happy to hang out together with you. Does Ari have here? I haven\u2019t seen it.<br>Fadli: I&#039;ve called him and he would come in 5 minutes.<br>Handi: I cannot wait to see him.<br>Dina: Yes, me too. He said that his business is so wonderful right now.<br>Fadli: So, what do you do now?<br>Dina: I was working at an insurance company and now I&#039;m trying a new hobby.<br>Fadli: I am curious about your hobbies. What is it?<br>Dina: Ask to Handi.<br>Fadli: Handi, tell me what your new hobby now? And I will tell my hobby that is very interesting for you to try.<br>Handi: Well, I&#039;ll tell you but you must tell your new hobby later. We have a hobby called Jumping Stilts and known as an extreme sport and is currently so popular in Indonesia.<br>Dina: Yes, we join with community of Jumping Stilts Indonesia and practice every week at different places. We tried this hobby because there was a friend who was very good at doing Jumping Stilts. We were interested in, and then try it until now. What about you? What is your new hobby?<br>Fadli: I have a hobby that is not far from you. It is also an extreme sport that is so famous all over the world.<br>Dina: Let me guess, is it Parkour?<br>Fadli: No, this is a Bungee Jumping. A very extreme sport for your adrenaline.<br>Handi: We&#039;ve heard for a long time and really got us interested. Can you tell me what places have you visited?<br><span>Fadli: Not many, but I&#039;m very lucky to get a chance to try the beautiful places. I visited Bali in Indonesia. I&#039;ve also been to Colorado, USA. It is the highest bungee jump in the world, positioned in 12th, located not far from the Grand Canyon National Park, USA. Has a 142m just above the Colorado River, right in the historic Navajo Bridge. With stunning wild amazing Grand Canyon make it a popular destination for bungee jumping.</span><br>Dina: Amazing. Your hobby is very spectacular and makes me want to try it.<br>Handi: You&#039;re crazy, it was great! Hey, Ari has come.<br>Fadli: Ari, why you so late? You missed the story on Bungee Jumping in Colorado.<br>Ari: I&#039;m stuck in traffic. How are you all? Pleased to meet you. Hi Dina? You&#039;re here too?<br>Dina: Of course, we&#039;re telling some of our new hobby. What about you?<br>Ari: Last week, I climb Semeru, and next week I wanted to Papua.<br>Handi: Climb Jayawijaya?<br>Ari: Of course, you want to come?<br>Fadli: Fantastic, you have a new hobby that is very interesting to try. I want to go with you next week. Incidentally, I want to take time off for a thing, but I decided to go with you.<br>Ari: Is that true? I&#039;m very glad if you could come. I have not talked to you and feel a togetherness as it used to. What about you guys? Handi, Dina, come or not?<br>Dina: I am going to come, and Handi would participate also.<br>Handi: Hey, I have not decided anything.<br>Ari: You have to come Handi, if you have the heart to let Dina walked alone up the Jayawijaya?<br>Handi: Let me join you all.<br>Fadli: This will be an amazing experience. We have never gone together since 6 years ago right?<br>Ari: I agree with you. This will be the best experience we have ever had. Ready to go to Jayawijaya?<br>Fadli, Handi, Dina: Of course.<span><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bahasa-inggrisnya-anak-itu-adlh-anak-yang-paling-mengecewakan-di-473",
            "question": "Bahasa inggrisnya Anak itu adlh anak yang paling mengecewakan di keluarga itu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>The boy is the son of the most disappointing in the <span>family</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "That kid is the most dissapointed kid in that family",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "make-a-dialogue-using-1asking-and-giving-2present-continous-t-824",
            "question": "Make a dialogue using :    1.Asking and giving \r\n2.Present continous tense\r\n3.Simple present tense\r\n4.Singular form\r\n5.Plural form",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple Present Tense<br>Habli : do you always breakfast every morning?<br>Dirga : yes i always breakfast every morning.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}